[Music]
for 125 years we have risen together
above every challenge
[Music]
just like the sun
that continues to shine
with warmth
and Hope
[Music]
We rise
to fulfill our commitment to you
and support you
as we journey to a bright New World this
has been our promise for 125 years
[Music]
to be with you
son
to rise with you
today
tomorrow
and Beyond lifetimes
foreign
and Welcome to our presentation the Sun
Life Insurance Philippines empowering
the Financial Security among the insure
but before that I will introduce the
brand Finance of this project
starting from button crystalline
plus Eliza Joy
and last but not least your study
urbistondo Shirley so now for the agenda
we'll be discussing four objectives the
introduction which includes the company
background dream history
ownership structure and board directors
products and services
and the most important thing
contributions to Philippine Financial
system and at the end of the
presentation you should be able to
explore the history
vision and vision of Sun Life Insurance
Philippines
second examine its ownership structure
third differentiate its products and
services
and lastly to evaluate the company
contributions in the Philippine
Financial system
Sun Life Insurance as a leading Global
Financial Services Company based out of
Canada offer abroad range Insurance
retirement and investment products and
services to meet the diverse needs both
of the individual and corporate clients
around the world
let's talk about the company background
of Sun Life Insurance Philippines
some live in the Philippines offers a
diverse range of insurance wealth and
Asset Management Solutions to help every
Filipino in their Journey towards a
brighter life Sun Life Insurance
Philippines also being the country's
first and longest standing life insurer
the history of sunlab insurance
Philippines
it was in 1895 three years before the
Republic of the Philippines was
officially founded when Sunday first
said put in the country with a mission
of giving Filipinos the opportunity to
enjoy the humanitarian benefits of
insurance in year 2000 they agreed with
yoshenko group of companies to create
Sunday group of financial incorporation
by year 2011 sunlight traded shares on
Philippine Stock Exchange for the first
time finally in 2015 the company
celebrated its 120th anniversary
as of 2020 to 2000 2023 sunlight holds
the number one position in the Life
Insurance sector with 215 branches
having been established in the
Philippines for 128 years
this is the mission and vision of
sunlight insurance
mission to help our clients achieve
lifetime Financial Security and lives
healthier lives
Vision to be one of the best insurance
and asset management companies in the
world
core values the first one is integrity
encourage support and reward for
contribute to the full extent of their
potential
engagement committed to the highest
standards of business ethics and good
governance client Focus provides some
Financial solution for clients and
always work with their interests in mind
Excellence pursue operational excellence
to Dedicated people quality products and
services and value-based risk management
value delivered value to the clients and
sharesholders they serve into the
communities in which they can operate
ownership structure Sun Life of the
Philippines offers individual and group
life and health insurance product to
individuals and businesses through a
fully owned subsidiary Sun Life of
Canada Philippines Incorporated and
through a joint venture with the
yochenko group Sun Life Grandpa
Financial Incorporated in which the
company has a 51 ownership State the
company also offers mutual funds through
another wholly owned subsidiary Sun Life
asset management company Board of
director first is Mr Benedito season he
is the CEO of sunlight Philippines he
joins sunlight Financial in 2010 and
serve as a Chief Financial Officer Asia
at sunlight Financial
next is Mr Alexander eston he's the
president of sunlight Foundation
Incorporated and sunlight Financial
Plans Incorporated he is a marketing
director in 1999 and a head of Metro
Manila new business offices of cluster 2
until 2009.
so next is Miss Valerie and Palma he is
the chief assistant manager management
officer next is Richard Esty the
president of sunlight Grappa Financial
Incorporated next is Miss Maria Josefina
a Castillo is the chief operating
officer
next is Michael geraldi Enriquez he is
the president or chief investment
officer
the next one is Miss Maria sachiko apang
Chief Financial Officer
next is attorney Edgar Esther
tordasillias he is the general counsel
the next one is subra ramakshinan he is
the chief business and formation officer
next one is
the president of Sun Life Asset
Management Incorporated
next one is Gab Mishra chief operations
and digital Enterprise of officer
and the last one is Miss Candy esterba
he's the Chief Financial Officer of Sun
Life Philippines
now I'm going to discuss the products
and services
income continuation the Sun starts up
it's a good choice for first-time
Insurance buyers and who want something
simple affordable and hassle-free in
application
second education the sun dream achiever
in a life insurance and savings plan is
increasing
it's increasing guaranteed cash benefits
ensure that child has school
guaranteed cash benefits ensure that
child has six School funds no matter
what happens
let's talk about investment the mutual
funds are a great way to maximize your
earning potential next the standard
Prosperity Bonds have historically
generated higher returns compared to
traditional deposit products today
everyone I am Christian and today we
will talk about the insurance coverage
of sunlight Philippines
reinsurance offers coverage for everyone
in the family from young to old up to
100 years old
gives a large amount of money to the
people who depend in the insured after
they pass away
ensures the family can go financially if
they insured faces an unfortunate event
covers 36 serious health conditions and
operations like cancer paralysis kidney
failure and a lot more
we offer a benefit that protects against
any of the serious health issues that
are included we also provide a cash lump
some benefits of at least 50 000 to 5
million pesos
adaptable and personalized plan based in
your business needs and last insurance
will end when a serious health condition
or death is compensated and for The
Accidental benefit
we offers extra benefit if the insured
dies unexpectedly because of an accident
laws of claims or vision benefits is
given if the insured passes away or
suffered amputation or blindness in the
accident
and for the projected benefit
obligations
first benefit amounts that are probable
to be paid at various future times
second obligations refers to the
complete sum of condensation that
workers are eligible to receive for
their services and third to determine if
pension plans have institution funding
calculations must be acquired and last
we will talk about the contribution to
the financial system
Sun Life Insurance offers a diverse
array of insurances retirement and
investment products and solutions
catering to individual and businesses
worldwide furthermore it plays a pivotal
role in supporting corporate expansion
and infrastructure development through
its commitment to a long-term investment
in addition to its corporate in divorce
the institution extends the
accessibility of financial services to
Encompass participation from the
communities
the Border public and government
entities
one of its notable initiatives involves
enhancing access to the secure savings
and transactional solutions through
public banking moreover
its contributions extend beyond the
financial Rin and it's Aid the
government in generating Revenue through
the collection of taxes regulatory fees
and levies imposed on various financial
institutions